ecs.com.tw 2017-11-20

# ECS - Motherboard, Notebook, Tablet PC, System, IPC, LIVA Mini PC

Privacy Policy

Elitegroup Computer Systems Co., Ltd. and its affiliates (together referred to as "ECS") take the private nature of your personal information very seriously. To comply with Personal Information Protecting Act and applicable laws, ECS frames Privacy Policy (the "Policy") and outlines what personal information we may collect, how we use and safeguard the collected personal information and with whom we may share it. Your accessing of our website at [www.ecs.com.tw](http://www.ecs.com.tw/) (the "Website") will be deemed that you accept this Policy. Please read it carefully. 

### Personal Information Collected

You do not need to provide any personal information for the use of this Website. However, there are circumstances that ECS may ask you to provide us with certain personal information for some services provided by ECS on the Website (including but not limited to product support, registration, event or activities). When you submit personal information (such as your name, mailing address, email address and other contact information), it constitutes your consent to the use of such information for the purpose(s) stated below.

### Use and Disclosure of Personal Information Collected

  * The personal information ECS collected is used to respond to your inquiries that you request and to help ECS to upgrade the quality of the Website and the services that ECS provides over the Website. ECS will not disclose, sell or provide your personal information to any third party except the situations stated in this Policy.

  * ECS may collect your "device data" such as products model/serial number, preferred interface, language settings, frequently used software information, the software function usage behavior 

    * to provide you with better services, enhance user experience, and continuously discover problems to improve performance; and/or

    * to obtain customer feedback and to analyze user experience. ECS reserves the right to provide such information to our officers, employees, contractors, agents, and designees to the extent necessary to enable them to execute certain web services (such as web hosting or maintenance services) for us.

  * ECS also reserves the right to disclose your personal information to any third party if we believe that we are required to do so for any of the following purpose:

    * by law; 

    * to comply with legal processes or governmental requests;

    * to prevent, investigate, detect or prosecute criminal offences or attacks on the technical integrity of the Website or our network; and/or 

    * to protect the rights, property, or safety of ECS, the users of the Website, or the public.

### Transfer of Personal Information to Different Locations

When you submit personal information to ECS, you understand and agree that this personal information may be transferred between ECS and its affiliates and/or agents and/or contractors of ECS internationally, and may be stored and processed in any of the countries where ECS and its affiliates and/or agents and/or contractors located. All transfer, storage and use of your personal information shall be subject to and protected by this Policy.

### Web Traffic-related Information

ECS's web server automatically records certain information incidental to your use of our Website, such as the name of your IP address of the computer you are using, the type of browser software and operating system that you use, and other similar web-traffic information. Information regarding your traffic patterns may be aggregated to compile a web transaction report showing web-traffic related information, but in no event shall ECS use any of your web-traffic related information for any purpose beyond this Policy.

### Access Personal Information

Unless otherwise specified in applicable laws and regulations, you may exercise the following rights with regard to your personal information upon written request: 

  * any inquiry and request for a review of your personal information; 

  * any request to make duplications of your personal information; 

  * any request to supplement or correct your personal information; 

  * any request to discontinue the collection, processing or use of your personal information; and

  * any request to delete your personal information. 

### Revision to Privacy Policy

ECS reserves the right to modify this Policy at any time and publish on the Website after such modification. We therefore suggest you access the Site regularly to ensure that you know the latest version of Policy. 

### Contact ECS

If you have any inquiries, questions, comments or complaints about this Policy, please feel free to contact us by using the contact information provided in "Contact Us" of the Website.

Version updated on July 1, 2015.
